

Oakville, ON, Canada

□ (+1) 2892596430 | ☑ liuwilly4@gmail.com | 🏕 palmswill.github.io/react-resume2021/ | ☑ palmswill | 🛅 williamliucs

Summary

2+ years React-based web developer with experiences in business management and sales campaigns on e-Commerce platforms with front-end knowledge such as React library, HTML5, CSS3 and back-end knowledge such as NodeJs, Express REST API, Amazon S3, fire base and google API. Currently studying in Sheridan college and looking for internship focusing on modern web development.

Professional Experience _____

Tribute Window Coverings

Mississauga, Canada

SUPPLY CHAIN & PRODUCT SUPPORT MANAGEMENT

Nov. 2017 - Present

- Generating daily sales and inventory report, estimating the needed purchase based on report status. Accurately predicted sales trend preventing over or shortage of stock reducing department back-order rate by 20% in 2018 comparing to previous years.
- · Communication between vendors. Negotiated the price and brought down the cost of product in charge for more than 10%.
- Provided product support for mechanical products, created online instruction videos and product manual receiving over 80 % positive feedback and product sales was observed to increase by more than 10% in the same period.
- · Technical supported the company, including computer set up, software problems encountered etc. Reduced the IT support cost per month for more than 20 %.

Taiwan Intelligence Service Corps,

Taichung, S.Taiwan (Remote)

April 2019 - April 2021

ASSOCIATE ARCHITECTURE AND SYSTEM DESIGNER (CONTRACT)

- improved performance by redesigning database and created and modify user interface.
- · created and modify user interface ,use cases and user flow design by communicating with the clients
- Created detailed user manuals and release including issues and bug tracking

Mini Micro Mississauga, Canada

WAREHOUSE MANAGEMENT /E-COMMERCE ASSISTANT

September 2017 - November 2017

· Held sales campaign increasing online visibility and planning of market strategy

Skills

Languages: JavaScript ES6,HTML5,CSS3,Java

Front End Libraries & Tools: ReactJ(Router, Redux Toolkit, Context API etc), Semantic UI, Bootstrap

Back Ends: NodeJs, Amazon S3, Google API, Firebase, Auth0

Others Data analysis, Tech Support, Database Design, Microsoft Office, ERP, Quickbook

Projects _____

TWC E-Commerce Project

HTTPS://E-WEBSITE-TCC.HEROKUAPP.COM/

Julv. 2021 - Present

• Built with MERN stacks combing with ERP database and Amazon S3 image cloud and autho authentication. (Currently in progress)

Spacetagram

HTTP://NASAPOD2021.HEROKUAPP.COM/

September,2021

• A responsive NASA picture of the day Liker, built with React, Semantic UI & NASA POD API

The Shoppies

HTTPS://MOVIECHALLENGE2021.HEROKUAPP.COM/

April,2021

· A Movie Nominator Built with React, Semantic UI and Movie IMDB API

Education

Sheridan College Oakville, Canada

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT & NETWORK ENGINEERING (GPA:3.6/4)

Sep. 2020 - April. 2023

• Relevant Courses: Enterprise Java, Web Programming, Interactive User Design, UX/UI Design

BYUNGJIN PARK · RÉSUMÉ **SEPTEMBER 20, 2021**